[The Demon Hunter's Romance]
[Episode 34]
Jiu, it's time.
Let's go.
Why make such a fuss?
Our Master said
tonight is your big moment.
There can't be any slip-ups.
Uncle
is really attentive to me.
This way, please.
It's even quieter
than last time.
All the shops are closed too.
Besides the waterways, they've also
locked down the entire city.
Seems like
your guess might be correct.
Humans are cunning.
No matter what happens,
it's always right to assume
the worst.
Let's head for the Sky Cavern first.
Okay.
Let's go this way.
Be careful not to alert them.
Okay.
Jiu, here we are.
Manager Lyu.
There's a situation outside.
Our men don't know
how to handle it.
What's wrong?
Nothing serious.
I'll go fix it.
Jiu, please go ahead.
I'll be there soon.
Okay.
This is heavily guarded.
I'll go in and check.
Do you have a plan?
Just fight our way in.
Don't be reckless.
They far outnumber us.
Do those weaklings even count as manpower?
Don't forget that
all your injuries
were caused by those "weaklings."
Quiet! Look.
Can't hear what they're saying.
There's a boat out there.
It surely carried someone.
"There's a boat out there.
It surely carried someone."
No matter who it is,
we can't let them mess up
the things at the Bone Washing Pool.
"We can't let them
mess up the things at the Bone Washing Pool."
"Kill any intruders you find."
-Yes.
The Bone Washing Pool?
Did they already get started?
I know that path. Follow me.
The Bone Washing Pool is over there.
I'll hold them off. You keep going.
Keep up.
Go.
Xuanye.
Uncle, is this
the Bone Washing Pool that you mentioned?
That's right.
This is where
you're going to
get a rebirth.
It's also the Gate connecting the two realms.
The 12th year is coming.
Xuanye,
Beyond this is your home,
the Carefree Land.
You know what?
I once accidentally entered that place
and saw one of the most unforgettable scenes in my life.
Demons and monsters abounded
and ran rampant;
each one was unbelievably strong and mighty.
Even if only one in 10,000
of such formidable demons come
to the mortal world,
it'll bring
catastrophic disaster to mankind.
But they can't.
I am from the Mystic Panther clan.
Our mission
is to guard this Realm Gate
and prevent the Carefree Land's demons
from coming to the human world.
Is that so?
But you came here.
So did your brother.
How can you guarantee they won't come?
And how can you ensure that the Mystic Panthers
will never change
and will always be able to fight off
other demon clans?
So,
Uncle, you established the Sky Cavern here
not for money,
but to guard the Realm Gate?
Of course.
The Sky Cavern's mission
is to fend off the demon clans
and guard the Realm Gate.
If things go south one day,
we will fight to the death.
Even if we have to blow up
the entire Underground City,
we must not allow demon clans
to set foot in the human world.
I guessed so.
What?
If it weren't to fight the demon clans,
why would you have carved
the demon-subduing formations all over the stone wall?
Xuanye,
you know, we humans
have a saying that goes,
"Those not of our kind can never be trusted."
Not all demons
are like you.
Everything I've done
is just for our survival.
Hope the demons won't come,
never come.
Uncle,
when did you
discover this place?
I told you
I once fell for a fox demon.
Later, she accidentally
hurt me,
so she left out of guilt.
Since then,
I've been looking for
a way to turn demons into humans.
Now,
I've worked it out,
but I can't find her anymore.
Have others tried it before?
Yeah, sure.
Otherwise, how could I dare to let you try?
Are you ready?
Xuanye.
Humans are born ignorant,
leading a sordid life of petty gains,
even unable to scratch the surface of what the world is really about.
They're naturally intimidated
by the unknown.
You know what?
Throughout history, those who made
great achievements weren't necessarily the smartest,
but definitely the bravest of their time.
Look.
The Path of Life is open.
Whether you want to live as a human
or remain a demon,
it's now
your call.
Please.
Get them!
Come on!
That way!
Stop there!
-Let's go.
-Go.
You're impressive fighters.
Miss Duan,
here we meet again.
Where's Xuanye?
Jiu's deeply in love with you,
yet you're hanging out with the demon who hurt him.
Aren't you afraid of breaking his heart?
You are the ones who want to hurt him!
We've helped you guys over and over again,
but you blindly trust a demon.
It's truly disheartening.
Cut the crap, dude.
We've already sent a message.
If we die here,
I swear
not a single living being
will survive in your Sky Cavern.
Catch them.
-Yes!
-Let's go!
No time to waste! I'm going to find Xuanye!
Not bad, Commissioner.
I am your superior.
If I couldn't outdo you,
how could I deserve my salary?
Oh, arrogance.
What's wrong?
Are you afraid now?
Uncle, you're right.
I am indeed afraid.
I am not the bravest
of our time.
Sorry for having troubled you, Uncle.
I need to ponder over
where my future path
should lead.
I'll take my leave now.
Stop there.
When did you find it out?
You were rushing it.
I haven't known you and Lyu
for very long.
Usually, you all maintain
a calm demeanor
come what may.
But you showed unusual concern only for
my demon-human transformation
in the Underground City.
I found it
a bit off back then.
Maybe it was just
out of our genuine concern for you.
That's
what I thought in the first place.
But soon,
I once again
lost consciousness and transformed
into a panther.
Could it be related to the Peerless Bracelet?
Yes,
I thought
the same the first time.
But the second time,
I was pretty sure that
someone was deliberately causing this.
Zi Kong was the only one who managed to
make it before.
So I went to find him.
Did you find him?
No, I didn't.
But I discovered
where you ambushed him.
The Eight Pillar Sect's Dragon-locking Formation
and the Underground City's pass token,
I do recognize them.
If Zi Kong
really got caught by you guys,
then who was the one
plotting against me?
Uncle,
I really can't figure out
what you are up to.
If you think I'm a demon,
you can just go ahead and kill me.
Why bother going to such lengths
to put on this show
of being a caring uncle?
Out of curiosity about
your views on the demon clans,
I went to
the 18 Stores
and checked the records of Song Qi's
entries and exits in the Underground City.
He has never left
the Underground City.
But you told me in your letter that
he had already been sent away.
So,
Uncle,
you were lying.
Our Sky Cavern is wealthy and powerful.
Perhaps we used some means
to send him away in secret.
No,
you killed him.
Over these years,
the Sky Cavern's been buying demons at high prices.
Many demon hunter friends of mine
are all your customers.
Even Jiang Shangyun and his disciple
were your honored guests.
[Jiang Shangyun]
The two of them
were also killed by you, right?
You've collected loads of demons.
Where are you hiding them all?
If I'm not mistaken,
you've thrown them all
into the Bone Washing Pool, right?
You used Banxia to lure me,
orchestrating a plan to drive me out of control,
just to make me
jump into the Bone Washing Pool
and get my demon bones.
You do have the guts then.
You knew I was up to something, yet you
still dared to come?
I had to figure out
what tricks you were playing.
Otherwise, I'd be a pain to live
on guard against you every day.
Aren't you afraid that
you might not be able to leave once you're here?
Are you going to kill me?
I've never offended you, have I?
If you want to kill me,
you've had so many chances to do it before.
Why did you have to wait until today?
This Bone Washing Pool
can't help me transform
from a demon into a human, I guess.
You want me to jump into it.
What exactly do you want?
My primordial spirit?
Or my physical body?
Your Sky Cavern
has been running in the Underground City for years.
You must have great ambitions.
Are you
plotting against the Carefree Land, Uncle?
Enough!
Alright.
Since you've already guessed it,
I won't beat around the bush.
Given our relationship,
as long as you jump into it on your own,
perhaps our Eight Pillar Sect
can still maintain some final dignity.
Jump!
Uncle,
stop joking around.
You want to kill me,
so there's already no dignity left
between the two of us!
Maybe it's not too late
to change your mind and stop here.
It's too late.
It's already been too late
since 12 years ago.
So cut the crap!
The Greedy Wolf Sword?
My stubborn old master
refused to pass down the Hidden Dragon Case
to me.
Instead, he insisted on
giving it to your unambitious father,
letting such a treasure end up
being held by a demon like you!
How ridiculous.
The Eight Pillar Sect values harmony with all beings
and going with the flow.
A radical man like you
could never understand it.
Let me go! Let go!
Banxia!
Xuanye!
The Bone Washing Pool can't help you
transform into a human.
Instead, it will kill you!
Get out of here now!
Let her go!
She has nothing to do with this!
She does have nothing to do with this.
So, Xuanye,
as long as you jump into
the pool on your own,
I'll let her go.
I'm a man of my word.
Xuanye, don't listen to his nonsense!
Shut up!
Xuanye,
her survival
is actually not decided by me.
It all depends on you.
You know I'm not
a patient person.
Push her down.
Good, you're here too!
Now you two brothers have gathered here.
Kill them!
Yes, Master!
Let's end this quickly.
That's also what I'm thinking.
Man Ying!
Do you still remember the skills
Father taught you?
Yes.
Good.
Then show me
how much progress you've made
after all these years in the human world.
Interesting.
Watch out!
I'll break this formation with Shao Li Lance.
If there's a chance,
take it and escape.
Once the formation is bust,
we'll both fall into the pool.
I have a plan.
Just do as I say.
But...
Don't argue.
I'm your older brother.
You should listen to me.
Lingying.
I'll kill you!
Youhuang.
Commissioner, I'm fine.
Youhuang...
Youhuang?
I truly underestimated you two.
However, this show
should come to an end now.
Man Ying,
I'm entrusting the Mystic Panther Clan and the Carefree Land
to you now.
You were too slow!
I was letting you win.
Funny. Then let's do it again!
I'd rather rest a bit.
Let's take a break.
Zi Kong,
what do you want to do when you grow up?
Like our father,
I want to be the clan leader
to protect the Carefree Land and Mystic Panthers.
What about you?
Me?
I want to
be your support.
If you really become the leader
of the Mystic Panther Clan in the future,
remember that
I'm also one of them,
and you should protect me too.
Of course.
No matter when,
I will always protect you.
Congratulations, Master,
on collecting 1,000 demons' bones!
You've transformed into a demon?
Ridiculous, huh?
I've actually turned into a demon,
what I hated the most!
I've become a demon.
Miss Duan,
I know you don't recognize me,
but do you remember
the human trafficker who sold you?
So beautiful.
I know, right?
It's pretty. I think...
This one is nice too.
I have some candy here. Come on.
That day in the filthiest, narrowest alley
of the Underground City,
I killed that demon,
avenging my entire family.
Fate does work in mysterious ways.
It was also on that day
that I met you.
You have nowhere to escape now.
Go back with me!
Let go of me!
You little brat, you...
I should say thank you.
You were the one
who brought me into the Carefree Land.
There,
I saw the origin of all demons,
the Carefree Herb.
That place was awash with primordial spirits.
I finally realized
why more demons would appear
every 12 years,
like a never-ending cycle with demons emerging infinitely.
I supposed that
if I could destroy the Carefree Herb,
there would be no more primordial spirits in this world,
and thus, no more demons as well.
But I hated myself
because I was human!
Humans can do nothing
in the Carefree Land!
I needed to find a way
to turn myself into a demon.
Only then can I sneak into the Carefree Land
and eliminate all the demons!
Is this the solution you've come up with
as a demon hunter?
That's right.
To get rid of demons,
I must become a demon first!
Dream on!
You're right. It is a dream.
But my dream
is about to come true,
while your dream
will never be realized.
Xuanye!
The Realm Gate is about to open.
Behold the doomsday for the demon clans!
Wait for another 12 years
if you want to enter the Carefree Land!
Seriously?
No one can stop me!
Open!
Now!
Fine.
Since you are stopping me from opening it,
I'll reduce the entire Underground City
and the whole Guangping City
to ashes right now!
Let's all die together!
Go to hell together!
The Origin-returning Sword?
The Origin-returning Sword!
I've planned for a lifetime,
giving it my everything.
How could I fail?
Banxia!
Banxia.
How are you doing?
This place is about to collapse.
You should leave now.
How could I possibly
leave you behind
and get out by myself?
I have no strength to leave.
Just go.
Banxia.
Xuanye,
there's no time to waste. You need to go now.
Banxia.
Forget me.
♫Wishing for a nice city♫
♫To idle away♫
♫Waiting for a light that won't go out♫
♫Seeing the moon rise and set♫
♫Condensing the past all into tears♫
♫To reflect the passion glowing in my eyes♫
♫Who forgot about the ups and downs of that long night's journey?♫
♫Leaving behind a pouring rain of love and hatred♫
♫Who remembers what's deeply engraved by fate?♫
♫A fleeting memory, yet love endures♫
♫The beginning of love♫
♫The return is yet unknown♫
♫Through endless days and nights♫
♫Where my heart leads me to♫
Banxia,
may you live a life free of worries.
♫Who is talking about never letting go of the memory♫
♫Dreaming about the intertwined joy and sorrow♫
♫Who knows the river of life winds through with twists and turns♫
♫A fleeting memory, yet love endures♫